<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="94">
	<author>KR-Softwares</author>	
    <version>1.3.0.0</version>    
	<title>
        <en>Invoices</en>
        <de>Rechnungen</de>
    </title>    
	<description>
        <en><![CDATA[You do work for someone else?
Then just invoice your working time!

With this mod you can send invoices to another farm. There are predefined activities for this.
In the main menu you can create and pay invoices.

Changelog v1.3.0.0:
- Courseplay custom fields are now listed.
Changelog v1.2.0.0:
- Fix UI-Bug at prices (done by Bz455)
Changelog v1.1.0.0:
- Own text can be defined for each entry
- Own price can be defined for each entry
- Position "Goods" with unit liter added]]></en>		
		<de><![CDATA[Du erledigst Arbeit für jemand anderes?
Dann stelle doch einfach deine Arbeitszeit in Rechnung!

Mit diesem Mod kannst du Rechnungen an einen anderen Hof senden. Dafür gibt es vordefinierte Tätigkeiten.
Im Hauptmenü kannst Rechnungen erstellen und bezahlen.

Changelog v1.3.0.0:
- Selbst erstellte Feldränder werden mit aufgelistet.
Changelog v1.2.0.0:
- UI-Bug bei Preisen behoben (durchgeführt von Bz455)
Changelog v1.1.0.0:
- Eigener Text kann zu jedem Eintrag definiert werden
- Eigener Preis kann bei jedem Eintrag definiert werden
- Position "Waren" mit Einheit Liter hinzugefügt]]></de>	
		<es><![CDATA[¿Trabajas para alguien más?
Entonces, ¡factura tu tiempo de trabajo!

Con este mod se pueden enviar facturas a otra granja. Hay actividades predefinidas para ello.
En el menú principal puede crear y pagar facturas.

Registro de cambios v1.3.0.0:
- Les champs personnalisés de Courseplay sont désormais répertoriés.
Registro de cambios v1.2.0.0:
- Fix UI-Bug at prices (done by Bz455)
Registro de cambios v1.1.0.0:
- Se puede definir un texto propio para cada entrada
- Se puede definir un precio propio para cada entrada
- Se ha añadido la posición "Mercancías" con la unidad de litro]]></es>	
		<fr><![CDATA[Tu fais du travail pour quelqu'un d'autre ?
Alors pourquoi ne pas facturer ton temps de travail ?

Avec ce mod, tu peux envoyer des factures à une autre cour. Il y a des activités prédéfinies pour cela.
Dans le menu principal, tu peux créer des factures et les payer.

Changelog v1.2.0.0 :
- Correction d'un bug de l'interface utilisateur au niveau des prix (fait par Bz455)
Changelog v1.1.0.0 :
- Un texte propre peut être défini pour chaque entrée
- Un prix propre peut être défini pour chaque entrée
- Position "Marchandises" avec unité litre ajoutée]]></fr>	
		<it><![CDATA[Lavori per qualcun altro?
Allora basta fatturare il tempo di lavoro!

Con questo mod potete inviare fatture a un'altra fattoria. Ci sono attività predefinite per questo.
Nel menu principale è possibile creare e pagare le fatture.

Cangelogramma v1.2.0.0:
- Correzione del bug dell'interfaccia utente sui prezzi (fatto da Bz455)
Changelog v1.1.0.0:
- Possibilità di definire un proprio testo per ogni voce
- Il prezzo proprio può essere definito per ogni voce
- Aggiunta della posizione "Merci" con unità di misura in litri]]></it>
    </description>    
	<iconFilename>Invoices.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>	
	<extraSourceFiles>	
		<sourceFile filename="Invoices.lua" /> 
	</extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>